<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-04-12T23:52:54+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Or Is It Imposter Syndrome</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/04/12/or-is-it-imposter-syndrome.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Or Is It Imposter Syndrome" /><published>2023-04-12T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-04-12T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/04/12/or-is-it-imposter-syndrome</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/04/12/or-is-it-imposter-syndrome.html"><![CDATA[<p>In my experience, I’ve found that having big, ambitious ideas is crucial to achieving meaningful results.</p>

<!--more-->

<p>However, I do have a tendency to get lost in my thoughts and procrastinate. Sometimes, I even complicate things unnecessarily.</p>

<p>Despite these challenges, I have achieved many things in the past and find great joy in doing so. So, I don’t think I purposely get in my own way.</p>

<p>Recently, I’ve been wondering if I’m capable of the tasks I’ve set before me or if I’ve taken on too much. Sometimes, I get hung up on minor design aspects of a project, and I’m not sure if it’s warranted or just me overthinking things.</p>

<p>While these thoughts may seem like the ramblings of a mad mind, they’re a natural part of my thought process as I work towards my goals. If you’re on mobile this site is another one of the few headaches I took upon myself just so I can actively work on these machinations of mine rather than toy with ideas in a playground I made for it of sorts. My realisation since has been, I know flexbox but do I know flex box?</p>]]></content><author><name>Neo</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my experience, I’ve found that having big, ambitious ideas is crucial to achieving meaningful results.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Journey</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/04/11/the-journey.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Journey" /><published>2023-04-11T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-04-11T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/04/11/the-journey</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/04/11/the-journey.html"><![CDATA[<p>…and so begun my diving head first into the unknown.</p>]]></content><author><name>Neo</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[…and so begun my diving head first into the unknown.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Real About Me</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/04/11/the-real-about-me.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Real About Me" /><published>2023-04-11T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-04-11T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/04/11/the-real-about-me</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/04/11/the-real-about-me.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello, I’m a highly proficient full-stack developer with fluency in
C, C++, Python, CSS, JavaScript, and SQL.</p>

<!--more-->

<p>I specialize in web development using the Flask framework and have extensive experience
in building complex web applications using this technology stack.
With my solid understanding of programming principles and ability to
write scripts and programs in multiple languages, I bring
versatility and adaptability to every project I work on. Whether
it’s building a database-driven web application or creating a robust
backend infrastructure, I have the expertise to get the job done.
I’m a committed and dedicated individual who consistently strives to
improve my skills and knowledge in the field of software development.
If you’re looking for a skilled and talented developer who can
deliver high-quality results, look no further!</p>]]></content><author><name>Neo</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I’m a highly proficient full-stack developer with fluency in C, C++, Python, CSS, JavaScript, and SQL.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Things You Would Probably Know</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/04/11/things-you-would-probably-know.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Things You Would Probably Know" /><published>2023-04-11T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-04-11T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/04/11/things-you-would-probably-know</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/04/11/things-you-would-probably-know.html"><![CDATA[<ul>
  <li>I’ve lived in 3 countries proper, South Africa, Canada and currently Zambia</li>
</ul>

<!--more-->

<ul>
  <li>I’m currently trying to figure out my perfect trajectory</li>
  <li>Complacency was the reason I left my last job, consider it one of many</li>
  <li>Ich kann Deutsch sprechen, verstehe mehr als ich sprechen kann. Englisch ja?</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Neo</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve lived in 3 countries proper, South Africa, Canada and currently Zambia]]></summary></entry></feed>